<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on wtimme</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on wtimme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 19:22:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wtimme.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From the time that I almost helped people with Corona symptoms</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/kvhh-covid-check/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 19:22:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/kvhh-covid-check/</guid><description>In this post, I will talk about how I almost created a web app that helped people with Covid-19 symptoms while I was in quarantine myself. And why it was shut down eventually.
Back in mid-2020, when the first &amp;ldquo;wave&amp;rdquo; of Corona was hitting Germany and people were getting more and more cautious about personal contact and transmission of the disease, I had just returned home from a long-planned vacation in Germany&amp;rsquo;s south, in Bavaria.</description></item><item><title>Software Recommendations</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/software-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 13:22:13 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/software-suggestions/</guid><description>On this page, I&amp;rsquo;ll collect software that makes my life easier.
Essentials Name Details OS KeePassXC Cross-Platform, Open Source password manager Linux, macOS, Windows Syncthing Cross-Platform, Open Source file synchronization without a &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; Linux, Windows, macOS, Android Messaging Name Details OS Signal Cross-Platform, Open Source Messenger iOS, Android, Linux, macOS, Windows Audio &amp;amp; Video Name Details OS youtube-dl Downloads videos from a lot of sites, e.</description></item><item><title>Crawling the App Store</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/crawling-the-app-store/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 12:48:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/crawling-the-app-store/</guid><description>On this page, I collect my research results for App Store crawlers. The page&amp;rsquo;s goal is to act as a starting point for people who want to crawl the App Store and aggregate information from it.
Existing crawlers This list was compiled by searching for &amp;ldquo;app store crawler github&amp;rdquo;.
Last updated: February 28th, 2021
Project Store Language Stars Forks Last commit Joeeyy/app_crawler App Store Python 7 2 10 Nov 2020 mladerman/iTunes-App-Store-Crawler App Store Python 40 21 31 Jul 2012 obersoy/Apple-Store-Crawler App Store C# 7 17 11 Nov 2014 alessandrodd/playstore_crawler Play Store Python 9 3 1 Sep 2020 nowa/iOS App Store Crawler (Gist) App Store Ruby 12 1 4 Aug 2010 fermanjj/App-Store-Scraper App Store Python 1 2 29 Jan 2018 facundoolano/app-store-scraper App Store JavaScript (Node.</description></item><item><title>Migrating to Hugo</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/migrating-to-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 12:32:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/migrating-to-hugo/</guid><description>I have migrated the page to Hugo, which should be more future-proof. After not posting for a while, I thought to give blogging (well, writing) another try in order to have a place where I can write down some thoughts.</description></item><item><title>iTunes Review Watcher</title><link>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/2015-04-12-itunes-review-watcher/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 18:20:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://wtimme.github.io/posts/2015-04-12-itunes-review-watcher/</guid><description>Introduction In my sparetime I&amp;rsquo;m creating a iOS application that focusses on customer reviews on Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store. It consists of the native app (written in Objective-C, as of now) and a REST server that gathers all the information from Apple&amp;rsquo;s servers.
As much as I love happily coding away, I also appreciate our users' feedback. For iOS applications, a very common way of receiving feedback are the reviews on the iTunes Store.</description></item></channel></rss>